本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译制作，仅供学习，禁止用于任何商业盈利行为。若因私自散布传播造成法律问题，本字幕组概不负责。更多影视请搜索并关注新浪微博@大家字幕组。
把这拿开 太恶心了
Don't use that one. It's icky.
上帝不允许这样做
God doesn't make mistakes very often,
既然发现了
but when he does,
EVERYONE
你就该让它在垃圾桶待着
You have to throw them right in the trash.
关注新浪微博
@大家字幕组
这也太离谱
Does this make sense
扫扫加微信
了点吧?
to anyone else?
白裙子 30美金
White dress, $30.
大家字幕组
微 信 关 注
dajiazimuzu
白色婚纱裙 200美金
White wedding dress, $200.
dajiazimuzu
里面藏了可卡因还是什么?
Is there cocaine in this or something?
没错 婚纱厂就是家毒巢
Yeah. The wedding industry's a racket.
扫扫加微信
嘿 你觉得啥都是毒巢
Oh, you think everything is a racket.
dajiazimuzu
扫扫加微信
大家字幕组
格林 这是最后一支
And that is the last of it, Glenn.
我知道大家想说什么
I'm just gonna say what we all thinking.
真是美爆了
This is pretty as hell.
正好8点
Oh, it's 8:00.
等等
Ooh, wait. Uh, hold on.
我想调整一下
I just want to move that.
它歪了
That's not in center.
应该放中间的
That should be in center.
剩下的五个小时要卖什么
Well, what else a good use of the last five hours.
超级商店
第一季 第八集
大家字幕组 欢乐出品
翻译  苏沐秋  Marry  Harrio
她们知道自己就是在抢一件上面有亮片的
They realize they're basically just fighting over a white net
白色网纱 对吧?
with glitter on it, right?
我压5美元那个金发的赢
Mm, I got five bucks on the blonde.
校对  苏沐秋
没错 我也是
Yeah, I'll take that action.
怎么有那么多退回的商品?
How are there already this many go backs?
这才开门5分钟呢
We've been open for five minutes.
我今天是来买东西的
Oh, I'm actually here as a customer today.
时间轴  喻心黄速西子耶  马路边
这包配我吗?
How do I look?
这表情不错
Aw, that's hella nice, yo.
笔记本电脑在哪?
Yo, where's the laptops at?
压制  冰岛
我们大概需要五六台
We need, like, five or six of those things.
我的乐队要来参加我们的婚礼
My band is playing at our wedding.
我们准备到时砸电脑狂欢
Yeah, we're gonna smash computers as part of the act
你懂的 大家都喜欢电子产品
'cause, you know, like, technology.
这听起来像场奢侈的庆典
That sounds like an expensive celebration you're planning.
大约500号人呢
It's about 500 people.
本来想请多点的
I wanted to invite more,
但手头有点紧
but I couldn't afford any more stamps.
我猜你们父母肯定说了
I bet your parents are all, like,
"别把钱全花了!
"Don't spend all your money on one day!
留点给孩子"
Save some for the baby."
爸妈都这样
Parents.
这儿有5000美金
Nah. Five g's, son.
出大事啦? 天上掉钱了!
Yo, what's up? Making it rain!
滚开 把钱留下
Stand down. Drop that paper, yo.
这是我的
It's mine.
这钱哪来的?
Where did you get all of that?
一位老妇女开着时速70的
Bo got hit by a car in the seventh grade
车撞到了小博
by an old lady.
她老花又醉驾
She was legally blind and super drunk.
他运气好吧?
Isn't he lucky?
我当时正在过马路
Yeah, your boy here was just crossing the street,
然后突然间 碰!
then it was like, crash!
看着那车灯
Oh, going to the light.
我大叫"我的主" 然后
I'm like, "No, god." Later.
我开始讹她 等等 女士
I got stuff to accomplish. Later, light.
我拿起手机
I pick up a phone.
"嘿 律师吗?
"Yo, hello, lawyer?
庭外和解?
Yo, settle out of court?
我正打算这样 好的"
I think so. Yes."
啪 钱来了
Wha-chaah. Money.
然后你就拿着5000美金走了?
So you just walk around with $5,000 in your pocket?
没错 我一直放在这边
That's right. I always got that right here.
哦 我的钱呢?
Uh-oh. Where's that five g's?
逗你玩的 傻瓜
Yo, I was just kidding, dummies.
我放在了另一边 不
I got that right here. Oh, no.
天呐 去哪了?
Yo, where's it at, for real?
都在那
It's right there.
我傻了?
Oh, what's up?
好眼力
Good looking out, yo.
不用小费
Please don't tip me.
夫人 我的手劲儿跟黑猩猩一样大
Ma'am, I have the arm strength of a chimp,
但还是拉不上去
but there is just too much real estate back here.
我可能得掰一下你的肩膀了
I'd have to dislocate your shoulder.
来吧
Do it.
别忘了提醒一下你的伴娘
But you'll have to teach one of your bridesmaids
这样做
to do this on the day.
他们是存了点钱
And they actually have money saved up,
但不是给宝宝存的
but instead of using it to pay for the baby,
他们想全砸在某场大派对上
They're gonna blow it all on some big party.
什么?
What?
2位17岁的青年要做个愚事?
Two 17-year-olds are making a bad decision?
不是吧?
What?
我以为这只会发生在电影里
I thought that only happened in the movies.
如我所说 我会希望有个人告诫我
I'm just saying that I wish somebody had warned me
别花太多钱在婚礼上
not to spend so much money on a wedding.
我想说
I'm telling you.
没人愿意让你教他怎么花自己的钱
People do not like to be told how to spend their money.
是吗?
Really?
所以意思是你不会再让我
So does that mean you'll stop telling me
给你"爸爸的朋友"打电话了?
to call your "Dad's friend"?
那是在让你赚钱
That's about making you money,
当你看到图表上的数据显示...
and if you saw the charts that he showed me...
对 图表
Oh, yeah. The charts.
嘿 白色闪光灯在哪呢?
Hi. Where are the twinkly white lights?
这是场户外庆典 所以一定要防水
It's an outdoor ceremony, so they have to be weatherproof.
- 我来带路 - 谢谢
- I will take you to them. - Thank you.
你们谁是那个幸运的小伙子?
Which one of you is the lucky fella?
其实就是我们俩
Oh, well, actually, we both are.
太棒了!
I love that!
四个人每年的纪念日
The four of you can celebrate
都能一起庆祝
your anniversary together every year.
- 不是... - 恭喜恭喜
- No... - Congratulations
- 祝福两位新人! - 是的
- On your wedding! - Yes.
永结同心
To each other.
- 祝福... - 谢谢
- To... - Yeah.
户外灯光区在通道4
Outdoor lighting is in aisle four.
需要任何帮助 尽管开口
If you need anything else, just ask.
- 谢谢 - 谢谢
- Thank you. - Thanks.
购物愉快!
Have a heavenly day!
谢谢你
Thank you.
我不知道怎么回事
I don't know how,
你看起来对男同志很有一套
but you really seem to have a handle on this whole gay,
你知道...
You know...
马特奥 好样的!
That's great, Mateo!
祝贺你
Congratulations on that.
你知道的 我以为你也是
You know, I thought you might be,
但我... 我不确定
but I... I wasn't sure,
然后我就忘了
and then I forgot about it.
但现在我懂了 我太为你高兴了
But now I know, and that's terrific with me.
没错
Yeah.
我要狠狠地炸飞这外星小子
I'm about to blow up this alien so bad.
小夏 你知道孩子一出生就要花很多钱...
Chey, you know babies come with lots of expenses...
那是你二货父母会说的话
Is what your dumb parents would say.
记得吗 以前老碎碎念?
Remember, from before?
父母嘛
Aah, parents.
没错
Yeah.
不过你爸妈说得对
But your parents do make a good point.
我妈说我们要存点钱
Well, my mom said that we should save some money,
但是小博说"不要" 所以这真的很难
but then, Bo is all like, "Nah," so it's a tough call.
见鬼! 这些外星人也太聪明了吧!
Dang! Those aliens are smart as hell!
你想继续购物吗?
You want to go back to shopping?
- 好啊 - 嘿 伙计
- Yes. - Hey, guys.
想玩个新鲜游戏吗?
You want to play a different game?
- 尿布! - 砰!
- Diapers! - Boom!
- 湿纸巾! - 炸!
- Wipes! - Blast!
- 热奶器 - 爆头!
- Bottle warmer. - Headshot!
- 再一个尿布 - 便便!
- More diapers. - Poo-poo!
- 抽乳器 - 喷射！
- Breast pump. - Squirt, squirt!
- 尿布包  - 灭了它!
- Diaper bag. - Pew, pew!
下地狱吧 小可爱们
See you in hell, cute baby stuff.
小博 它们全被你干掉了耶!
Bo, you're killing them all!
时间到
And time's up.
这是什么? 2500分!
What's up? 2,500 points!
宝贝我是不是能赢个香草可可软糖
Your boy here is getting a charleston chew!
事实上 那些不是得分
Actually, those aren't points.
是美金 这些东西的总价值
Those are dollars, and that's how much this stuff costs.
这些东西要2500美金?
This stuff is $2,500?
那是小博赔偿金的一半了
That's, like, half of Bo's stack.
还得加个汽车座 婴儿床和日托的费用
Plus a car seat and a crib and daycare,
然后还会源源不断的有东西要买
and it just keeps coming.
我得去碰好多次瓷
I'm gonna have to get hit by so many cars.
我们应该在婚礼上省着点
Maybe we should save some of our wedding money
为将来着想
for the future.
没错
Huh, yeah.
你能行的
You could do that.
为人父母
You do have to make some sacrifices
你必须有所牺牲
when you're a parent.
我的意思是 你整个世界天翻地覆
I mean, your whole life changes.
小博 你看起来有点奇怪
Bo, you look weird.
可能吧 呵呵
Yeah. Hey.
但是我觉得这样很好
But I think it's great
你们已经开始考虑到...
that you guys are starting to think about being...
妈呀!
Aah!
- 嘿 小心 - 小博?
- Hey, look out. - Bo?
麻烦让让 抱歉抱歉
Excuse me. Oh, sorry.
小博?
Bo?
我只想说"责任"而已
I was gonna say "Responsible."
你去哪了? 赶紧回来吧
Where did you go? Please come back.
我爱你
I love you.
我是夏安啊
It's Cheyenne, by the way.
我说 你干嘛非得要把这个小笨蛋吓成这样?
Hey, you had to go freak the little dummy out?
这不是我的错好嘛
Well, it's not my fault.
别怪她了 她说的对
Oh, she's right.
她只是告诉我们养孩子有多昂贵有多可怕而已
She was just teaching us this fun game
像个养成游戏似的
about how expensive and scary it is to have a baby.
如果他再也不会来了怎么办?
What if he never comes back?
不可能的 他会回来的
He will. He's gonna come back.
一定会的!
He will!
但是换个角度来说
And you know what?
如果他真的不回来的话
If he doesn't,
这也不是最坏的事...
that wouldn't be the worst thing...
你想说 还有更坏的 对吧?
Going right back at it, huh?
行吧
Okay.
那个啥 额 我去找他
You know what? Um... I'll go look for him.
你愿意的话 可以跟我一起找
Could tag along with me if you want.
那个傻逼把商店里的扫码机带走了
That turd walked out with a cloud 9 scanner gun.
这就是老娘的管辖范围了
That makes it my jurisdiction.
他不是傻逼
He is not a turd.
他绝对是个傻逼
Oh, he's a turd.
另外 我的车里有一种很奇特的味道
Also, my truck has a rather unique odor,
但是几小时之后你就会习惯了
but you should get used to it after a couple of hours.
我看还是算了吧... 谢谢邀请
Oh... No, thank you.
但是咱们还是分开找吧
We should probably just split up, you know,
还能扩大点搜查范围
cover more ground.
随你便 噢...
Up to you. Oh...
差点把我的电击枪忘了
Almost forgot my taser.
好吧 我跟你一起去!
Okay. I'm coming with you!
好好看着她
Take care of her.
好了好了 别哭了
Uh, hey, hey. Now, now.
一切都会好起来的
Now, now. There, little lady.
孩子乖 不哭不哭... 不会有事的
You're gonna... you're gonna do just fine, kiddo.
小姑娘乖
Girl.
我跟温蒂·威廉姆斯学的
I learned that from Wendy Williams.
如果你饿了的话 可以吃点黄豆罐头
If you're hungry, that can of beans is up for grabs,
但是这一罐不行
but not this one.
我不饿
I'm good.
我能听一下... 你的收音机呢?
Do you mind if I turn on the... where's your radio?
哦 我特意要了一辆没有收音机的车
Oh, I special ordered my truck without one.
还需要一点额外费用
Yeah, it costs a little extra,
但能减少小偷对这辆车的注意
but it makes the vehicle less appealing to thieves
没人想要一辆没有收音机的车吧
'cause no one wants a truck without a radio.
你说个歌名吧 我唱给你听
Name a song, though. I'll sing it for you.
- 算了算了 - 没事 你说吧
- That's okay. - No, no, go ahead.
我对音乐过耳不忘
I got a photographic memory for music.
好的吧 额...
Okay, um...
《单身女郎》吧
"Single ladies."
我没听过这首歌
Not familiar with that one.
- 火星哥的呢? - 不知道
- "Uptown funk." - don't know it.
- 《舞会皇后》 - 不晓得
- "Dancing queen." - nope.
《颤栗》?
"Thriller?"
迈克尔·杰克逊的歌?
Michael jackson?
你不能只说一些
You can't name a song by some guy
你中学同学唱的歌啊
you went to middle school with.
你得说点有名的
It has to be popular.
*哦 丹尼男孩*
*Oh danny boy*
*笛声在声声呼唤着你*
*The pipes the pipes are calling*
我不能当单亲妈妈的
I can't be a single mom.
我从没在高速公诉上驾驶过
I have never even driven on the highway before.
如果宝宝要去市中心怎么办?
What if the baby needs to go downtown?
好了好了 再说一次 小博会回来的 好么?
Okay, again, Bo is coming back, all right?
等他回来的时候 你要准备好
And when he does, you're gonna have a cart full
一车子全新的婚礼用品给他看
Of hella radical wedding stuff to show him.
对啊 就像这些
Yeah, like these little ass pillows
用来放重要戒指的小枕头
To put the rings on 'cause they're important.
小博曾经在我奶奶的退休派对的
Bo once threw up on a pillow
一个枕头上吐过
at my grandma's retirement party.
我看到的所有东西都在提醒我 他有多好
Everything I see reminds me of how amazing he was.
行吧 出乎意料的触发因素
Okay. Surprising triggers.
我们帮你选吧 你觉得哪个好?
We'll pick for you. What do you think?
这个 完事
This one. Done.
继续
Moving on.
- 喔 - 干嘛 不行么?
- Ooh. - What? What's up?
这个是麻布的
It's a little burlapy.
她是要结婚 不是要去送咖啡
She's getting married, not shipping coffee.
咱们还是选这个吧 怎么样?
Why don't we just go with this one?
这样吧 你自己决定
Well, you know what? Your call.
你是想要这个温暖而质朴的麻布呢?
Do you want to go warm and rustic like this burlap one
还是这款烂大街的?
Or generic, kind of unoriginal?
我觉得 还是温暖质朴的吧
I guess warm and rustic.
温暖质朴! 好眼光
Warm and rustic! All right.
我们买了个小枕头
We got ourself a pillow.
婚礼列车上的下一件物品 贵宾册
Next up on the wedding train, guest books.
好的
Okay.
我对自己之前处理你和你朋友的事情的方式
I feel terrible about how I handled things earlier
感到抱歉
With your friends.
朋友? 不不不 他们不是...
Friends? Oh, they're not... no.
- 伙计 他们不是我的朋友 - 我很抱歉
They're not my friends, dude. - Oh, I'm sorry.
基蜜们?
Gay bffs?
我不懂该怎么说
I don't know the lingo.
听着 我只想让所有走进这家店的人
Look, I just want everyone who comes into this store
都能觉得宾至如归
to feel accepted.
你知不知道 在这整个促销中
But do you know that in this entire sale,
没有一个专柜是专为同志婚礼准备的
There is not one section dedicated to gay weddings?
同性恋和异性恋用的装饰是一样的
Gay people use the same decorations as straight people.
只不过我们用的更好
We just use 'em better.
这正是我想说的
That's my point exactly.
我的意思是 他们并不用遵循
I mean, they should not have to conform
别人的... 异性恋人们
to someone's... Hel... hetero normal ideal
关于婚礼的想法
of what a wedding should be.
你愿意帮我一起摆放这些东西么?
Would you be willing to help me put something together?
当然
Of course.
EVERYONE
大家字幕组
太棒了
Great.
我们要把那些人的想法完全去除掉
We're gonna take those guys' minds and blow them.
我不觉得这么漫无目的地驾驶是个好主意
I don't know if just randomly driving around is a good idea.
大家字幕组
青少年都去哪?
Where do teenagers go?
舞会
Prom.
这附近有舞会么?
Is there a prom around?
不 我只是说我们应该像青少年一样思考
No, I just meant that we should think like a teenager.
你说得对
Ah, yeah.
老妈 滚出我的房间
Hey, mom, get out of my room.
你根本就不明白我们这一代人的想法
You don't understand my generation.
啊 青春痘
Pimples.
一点都没用
It's not helping.
嘿 嘿 嘿 停停停
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait!
那是他么?
Is that him?
嘿! 嘿!
Hey! Hey!
停下! 是他 就是他
Stop! It's him, it's him.
追上去 快快快
Speed up. Go, go, go.
小博!
Bo!
等等 小博!
Hey, Bo!
我们想和你谈谈! 停下!
We just want to talk! Stop!
那是我们店里的购物车
That's one of our carts.
是我们店里的购物车
什么? 谁在乎啊? 小博!
What? Who cares? Bo!
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
谁在乎?
Who cares?
老娘在乎
I care.
你!
Hey.
这是云九商店的所有品
That is Cloud 9 store property!
不是的
No, it's not.
迪娜! 他要跑走了!
Dina! He's getting away!
小博！
Bo!
这不是 绝对不是
No, no, no. Absolutely not.
- 给我拿来 - 不是你们的购物车!
Give it to me. Hey. - It's not your cart!
我又琢磨了一下
You know, on second thought,
这个购物车应该不是我们店里的
I don't think that is one of our carts.
我们中午吃啥?
So what are we thinking for lunch?
三明治? 墨西哥卷?
Sandwiches? Burritos?
印度菜? 西班牙菜?
Indian? Tapas?
你闹哪样?
What is up with you?
你还想不想找小博了?
Do you even want to find Bo?
当然了
Yes, of course I do.
只是... 不用立马找到吧
Just... Maybe not right away.
我真的不着急回去 买打折婚礼物件
I'm really not anxious to get back to the wedding day sale,
好吧
Okay?
看到那些女人为了
Just seeing all those women celebrating,
找到另一半而庆祝
having found someone,
我又不会变得年轻
And I'm not getting any younger.
- 闻者流泪 - 有时候谈恋爱的确很操蛋
- Kind of a bummer. - Well, it can be hard to date.
如果你看到我谈过哪些人 你就懂了
If you'd seen some of the guys I dated.
同性恋 种族歧视
Gay. Racist.
渣男 染红发
Mean. Redhead.
这是一个人
That was all one guy.
我也谈过几个傻屌啊
Oh, I've dated some losers.
我谈过这么一个
I dated this one guy
只会说"巨蟒剧团"的名言
who would only speak in Monty Python quotes.
我前男友和我交往
The last guy I dated only hung out with me
只是为了和我爸下象棋
to play chess with my dad,
前前男友只是为了用我的冰箱
And the guy before that was just using me for my freezer.
我谈过三个
I dated three guys
他们只是为了接近我闺蜜 蕾妮
who were dating me just to get close to my friend, Rene,
而且蕾妮都不算漂亮啊
And Rene wasn't even that hot.
这和蕾妮无关
Whatever. This is not about Rene.
蕾妮听起来就是个小砸婊
Well, Rene sounds like a sack of crap.
没错 谢谢你
She was. Thank you.
我一眼就看穿了
I just call it like I see it.
哈
Yes.
有个... 同事
There is... a guy at work
我和他擦出了火花
that things have been getting pretty intense with.
真的? 谁啊?
Really? Who?
我本来不想和同事谈论私人生活的
Well, I don't want to talk about my personal life
但是我要说
with coworkers, but I will say
我和他现在你侬我侬得飞起
that there has been some ‭very heavy flirtation happening.
我每天得换好几套衬衫
I've been changing my shirt multiple times a day
因为上面全是爱情的结晶
just 'cause of all the pit stains.
棒棒哒
Steamy stuff.
这个咋样?
How's this?
挺好的
It's nice.
这个咋样?
How's this?
挺好的
It's nice.
够基了吗?
But is it gay enough?
我可不想过会后悔
I don't want to be kicking myself later
因为没有特别基
that we should have gone more gay.
让我们在搞基这条路上渐行渐远吧
Let's err on the side of gay.
这个绝对够基了
It feels appropriately gay.
很好
Good.
我得说
You know, I have to say,
你比我想象中的要开明啊
you're much more open-minded than I thought.
谢谢
Thank you.
人们都以为基督教徒都憎恨同性恋
People assume all Christians are homophobes.
太无知了
You know, that is ignorant.
你都想象不到 被人带有成见地看待是多么得惨
You can't imagine how hard it is being stereotyped.
- 呵呵 - 我觉得
- Sure. - I mean, if anything,
耶稣费尽周折是来宽恕众生的
Jesus went out of his way to accept everyone.
- 同意 - 是吧
- Agreed. - Yeah.
我觉得耶稣应该只是同性结婚的
I think Jesus would've been pro-gay marriage.
肯定的
Absolutely.
他也会支持同性领养孩子
He would've been pro-gay adoption.
说不定 耶稣自己就是个基佬
For all we know, Jesus himself was gay.
今天周二 是吧?
So it's Tuesday, right?
就是说... 明天就周三了
That means... that means Wednesday's coming.
要奶昔吗?
Mm. Shake?
不用了 谢谢 素食者
No, thanks. Vegan.
我们可以继续找小博
You know, we can keep looking for Bo,
但他又不可能骑一辈子
But the guy can't bike forever,
就他那小身板
especially not with those quads.
你为啥不喜欢他?
What don't you like him?
因为小胡子?
Is it the mustache?
不是
No.
我19岁结婚
I got married at 19.
我知道他们怎么想的
I know what they're in for.
你会错过很多东西
I mean, you miss out on a lot of stuff.
你当然也会得到一些东西
I mean, you get stuff too, obviously,
但手头经常很紧
But the money's always tight,
然后总是好高骛远
And you're five steps ahead of where you should be
但懒癌晚期
but also five steps behind where you should've been.
但那小胡子也是真丑 对吧?
But the mustache is bad, right?
金红色头发的娘炮就不该长胡子
Strawberry blondes should not be allowed to grow facial hair.
必须的
No.
应该写在宪法里
That should be in our constitution.
就是
Yeah.
我们该回去了
Well, we should probably go back.
天 真希望那些新娘都走了
God, I hope the brides have cleared out.
其实吧 没人会注意我们
You know, no one's really gonna notice
出来了一两个小时
if we're gone another hour or two.
那我们做什么呢?
Well, what would we do?
我们可以嗨一下
Oh, we could pamper ourselves.
格拉瓦角美体店
太棒了
Oh, yeah.
这地方比我经常去的
The place is way fancier
要高级一些
than my usual spot.
还有擦火药的湿巾呢
Moist towelettes to wipe up the gunpowder.
简直是公主的待遇
Man, I feel like a princess.
我看到一款蓝绿色的
I think I saw a turquoise one.
哈 蛋糕架
Boom, cake stand.
银盘 蕾丝装衬
Silver-plated, lace bows.
这就是高雅的诠释
This is all kinds of elegant.
如果有人推着装满高雅的手推车向你走来
If someone came up to you with a wheelbarrow full of elegance,
你得说"不好意思 哥们
You'd have to be like, "Sorry, homie.
我们已经非常高雅了"
We ass-deep in elegance."
这个真的很漂亮
That's really pretty.
是的 啊不是
Yeah, yeah, no.
这个吧... 其实
That would be... really,
很适合传统的结婚蛋糕
it'd be perfect for a traditional wedding cake.
- 是的 - 但我们主要在说
- Yeah. - But we were talking more of,
向甜点盘那样的东西
like, a dessert pot luck kind of a thing.
婚礼上用? 太潮了点吧
For a wedding? ‭That seems a little adventurous.
乔纳说很多婚礼都开始加入DIY元素了
Jonah says a lot of weddings are doing more DIY elements.
我们只是在想
We're just looking for something a little more
特别为夏安和小博定制的婚礼...
specifically curated to Cheyenne and Bo's...
又是那个词
Ugh, that word.
你说我每周只能说一次"定制"
You said I could say "Curated" once a week.
这周就用在此时了
I chose now as my time.
说实话 只要小博在那 我根本...
Honestly, as long as bo is there, I don't even...
慢着 当然 当然
Yeah, no, no, no. Totally, totally, totally.
我只是说 婚礼不能
I'm just saying, I don't think a wedding
一直那么俗套传统
needs to be stuck in stodgy, old traditions.
你的意思 婚礼就该在树上的小屋
Right, better to have the wedding in a treehouse,
大家一起用大号喝自制鸡尾酒咯
drinking artisanal cocktails out of a tuba.
DIY的元素让人觉得更个性化一些啊
A DIY element does add a certain personal touch to it.
这就是流行一时的 就像婚礼中夫妇跳舞进场一样
It's a trend, like dancing down the aisle.
就像说"我在吃果馅饼
You know, it's like, "I'm eating flan.
在吃果仁蜜饼"一样
I'm eating a baklava."
为什么我们就不能像个文明人一样
Why couldn't we just have a nice, classy cake
弄一个经典华丽的蛋糕?
like civilized human beings?
给我的味蕾一个护照
Give my taste buds a passport
它们不想呆在这了
because they're going around the world.
我来教你一些基础知识
Let's go over some basics.
拿起你的子弹
You're gonna take your mag.
平整的那面是弹夹的后方
The flat part is actually gonna go towards the back of the gun.
我最喜欢的叔叔是个警察
My favorite uncle was a cop.
他给了我一把22口径的作为我成人礼礼物
He got me a .22 for my quinceañera.
干得漂亮 我原来以为
Here, I thought you were just
你只是个第二漂亮的同事
the second-hottest girl at work.
你应该不时和我一起参加名流晚宴
Hey, you should come with me to celebrity night sometime.
他们会把别人的照片当靶子
They put pictures on the targets.
不是我吹
I don't want to brag, but last week,
上周我干掉了克里斯汀·斯图尔特
Kristen Stewart was my bitch.
我的天
Oh, my god.
是吧 真是超级爽
Yeah, it's really satisfying.
明天他们好像要弄一个"丑闻"的主题
I think tomorrow they're doing the whole cast of "Scandal."
所以 你就打算这么抛弃你的未婚妻?
So, you just gonna walk out on your fiancé?
你觉得这就是"你的使命"
You think that's "Where it's at?"
差不多吧 好吧
Kinda. Okay.
就好像 每个我认识的潮人都这么干
Like, everyone cool I know has done that.
基本是唱饶舌的 但事实上每个运动员都这么做
Most rappers. Literally every athlete.
你知道吗?
You know what?
夏安没你会更好
Cheyenne is better off without you.
这是什么
What's this?
"博·德瑞克·汤姆森
"Bo Derek Thompson.
以优异成绩毕业于哈佛医学院
Suma cum laude, harvard medical school.
心脏病学主任 琼斯·霍金斯"
Chief of cardiology, Johns Hopkins."
欸 电脑的模板或什么上面的
Yo, some of that's left over
还漏了几个字
from the computer template or whatever.
等等 这就是你这一整天都在做的么?
Wait, this is what you were doing all day?
投简历?
You were handing out resumes?
还有你名字是博·德瑞克?
And your name is Bo Derek?
是啊 就像你说的 养孩子很花钱
Yeah, it's like you said. Parenting's expensive.
必须为了孩子多赚点钱啊 是男人就要担起责任
Got to make some paper for that baby coming, be a man.
"1972年-1981年 Vogue杂志总编辑"
"Managing editor of Vogue, 1972-1981."
天哪 我很惊讶 真的
I'm impressed, actually.
哦 不 艾米 这些都是假话
Oh no, Amy. This is all lies.
哦 太惊喜了
Oh, what a surprise.
你挑了个白裙子 心机多么重
You picked a white dress. What a curveball.
因为这就是一场婚礼该有的样子
'cause that's exactly what a wedding should be,
哪哪都是心机
a series of curveballs.
朋友们 你们这么关爱我我真的很感动
You guys, it's really sweet that you care,
但是这两条裙子都好丑
but both dresses are fugly.
我反正觉得你的品味
I just think that your tastes are
跟我的奶奶应该很合
a little more along the lines of my grandmother's.
嗯哼 我觉得
Okay, well, I just think that
你的品味跟暗黑女王
your tastes are a little more along the lines
会更契合
of a wiccan space queen.
你说什么?
What?
那你梦想中的婚礼是怎样的?
What's your dream wedding, anyway?
一堆人在草坪里流大汗
A bunch of people sweating in a field
然后几个汉子读《绒布小兔子》选段吗?
While some jag reads from "The velveteen rabbit?"
你梦想中的婚礼是什么样的?
What's your dream wedding?
一个叫马修的白人开一辆米色丰田卡美瑞吗?
A beige toyota camry driven by a white guy named Matthew?
- 这是什么意思? - 你懂的
- What is that supposed to mean? - You know
你觉得呢? 你想要看起来像我阿姨琳达吗?
What do you say? You want to look like my aunt Linda?
你可不能穿件绿豆服结婚呐
You cannot get married in a green bean.
这边请
Right this way.
欢迎光临 很荣幸见到您
Welcome. We are happy you're here.
你们做的?
You guys made this?
这真的很棒
It's really nice.
你觉得这就很好了吗?
You think this is nice?
你最好做好心理准备
You better buckle in
因为狂欢才刚刚开始
'cause the party is just getting started.
是吗? 我们没讨论吧 啊 好吧
It is? We didn't discuss... okay.
嗷
oh.
快摆好造型 机不可失哟
Pose yourself. There's nothing like it.
潮
Vogue!
- 哇嗷 - 时髦
- Wow. - Vogue.
格林 这和我们说好的不一样!
Glenn, this isn't what we agreed on!
我做了几个小改变
I made a few tweaks.
我把我的安全搜索调到最高限度
I turned my safe search up to the max
然后百度了"世界上最基的派对"
And then googled, "World's gayest parties."
哇嗷
Wow.
听着 他很努力
Listen. He's trying.
他就是你爸两年前的样子
He's your dad, two years ago.
啊 好吧
Oh, okay.
耶
Yeah.
这很棒
This was great.
非常非常感谢
Thank you so much.
- 不客气 - 哦 又来一个
- You're welcome. - Oh, another one.
- 手举起来 - 好 好吧
- Get those hands up. - All right.
- 举手举手嗨起来 - 好的额
哇
Whoa.
你简直像个公主
You look like a princess.
你喜欢吗?
You like it?
这是法拉·亚伯拉罕系列的
It's from the Farrah Abraham collection.
谁是法拉·亚伯拉罕?
Who's Farrah Abraham?
少女妈妈 AV女优
Teen mom, porn star.
你见过就肯定认识她
You'd recognize her.
不要再跑掉了
Don't run away again.
我不会了
I won't.
现在我们有一堆事情要处理了
Now we got a bunch to figure out.
但是无论如何 我和你
But no matter what, you and me
一定要办个屌炸天的婚礼
are gonna throw a baller-ass wedding,
养个屌炸天的孩子
raise up a baller-ass shorty,
然后一起过屌炸天的日子
and have a baller-ass life.
我觉得你已经写好了我们的誓词了
I think you just wrote our vows.
我赌五毛他们也就能过半年
I give them six months.
我不确定
I don't know.
也许他们能给我们惊喜呢
Maybe they'll surprise us.
现在 让我们流点绿血看看 哦耶
Now, let's bleed some green! Yeah.
来吧 沐浴在这些中间吧
Come and get a... take a little shower in this stuff!
呃 对他们也许不要太乐观了
Or not.
让他们从一场嗨爆的派对开始吧
Let 'em start out with a fun party.
耶
Yeah.
嘿 话说
Hey, by the way,
我们之前说的 如果你告诉任何人
What we were talking about earlier, if you tell anyone,
我会把你的耳朵...
I will staple your...
这是朋友间的秘密
It'll stay between friends.
谢谢
Thanks.
把你耳朵订在墙上
Ear to the wall.
你打断了我的话 但是我到时候会这么订的
You interrupted, but that's what I'll staple.
你知道就行
Just know that.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 乔纳
Hey, Jonah.
天啊 你真搞笑
God, you are so funny.
妈呀 我去
Oh, shoot.
本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译
仅供学习使用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
彼以国士待我 我以国士待之
用过免费优质字幕服务 而又有能力的人
有义务将这个免费服务做下去
若有心加入我们
请联系QQ群：428872140
EVERYONE
大家字幕组